import { Question } from '@/src/types/questions'

const katakanaYouon: Question[] = [
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"kya\"?",
    "options": [
      "キャ",
      "チョ",
      "ジャ",
      "ミョ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "キャ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"キャ\"?",
    "options": [
      "hyo",
      "kya",
      "sho",
      "gya"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "kya"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"kyu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ニュ",
      "ビュ",
      "チャ",
      "キュ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "キュ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"キュ\"?",
    "options": [
      "pyo",
      "nyo",
      "kyu",
      "myo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "kyu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"kyo\"?",
    "options": [
      "ニャ",
      "キョ",
      "リョ",
      "ニョ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "キョ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"キョ\"?",
    "options": [
      "nyo",
      "myu",
      "kyo",
      "pya"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "kyo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"sha\"?",
    "options": [
      "ギャ",
      "ショ",
      "シャ",
      "ヒュ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "シャ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"シャ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ryo",
      "kyo",
      "sha",
      "ju"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "sha"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"shu\"?",
    "options": [
      "シュ",
      "ビャ",
      "ギュ",
      "ピュ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "シュ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"シュ\"?",
    "options": [
      "nyo",
      "cha",
      "shu",
      "pyo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "shu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"sho\"?",
    "options": [
      "ギュ",
      "ショ",
      "ヒャ",
      "ギャ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ショ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ショ\"?",
    "options": [
      "bya",
      "pya",
      "sho",
      "hyu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "sho"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"cha\"?",
    "options": [
      "リュ",
      "ピャ",
      "ニャ",
      "チャ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "チャ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"チャ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ju",
      "cha",
      "mya",
      "kya"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "cha"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"chu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ピュ",
      "ビョ",
      "チュ",
      "ニョ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "チュ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"チュ\"?",
    "options": [
      "chu",
      "nyo",
      "byo",
      "ryo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "chu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"cho\"?",
    "options": [
      "ジョ",
      "シャ",
      "チョ",
      "キョ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "チョ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"チョ\"?",
    "options": [
      "nyo",
      "myu",
      "chu",
      "cho"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "cho"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"nya\"?",
    "options": [
      "キュ",
      "ミュ",
      "ニャ",
      "ビャ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ニャ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ニャ\"?",
    "options": [
      "bya",
      "pyo",
      "sho",
      "nya"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "nya"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"nyu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ヒャ",
      "ニャ",
      "ニュ",
      "ビュ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ニュ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ニュ\"?",
    "options": [
      "hyo",
      "kyo",
      "myu",
      "nyu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "nyu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"nyo\"?",
    "options": [
      "ヒョ",
      "ニョ",
      "ギャ",
      "ジュ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ニョ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ニョ\"?",
    "options": [
      "gyo",
      "hyo",
      "kyo",
      "nyo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "nyo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"hya\"?",
    "options": [
      "ピュ",
      "キョ",
      "ヒャ",
      "ミャ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ヒャ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ヒャ\"?",
    "options": [
      "chu",
      "myo",
      "hya",
      "myu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "hya"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"hyu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ギョ",
      "キョ",
      "ヒュ",
      "ビャ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ヒュ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ヒュ\"?",
    "options": [
      "kyu",
      "mya",
      "hyu",
      "rya"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "hyu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"hyo\"?",
    "options": [
      "ジョ",
      "ピョ",
      "ニュ",
      "ヒョ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ヒョ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ヒョ\"?",
    "options": [
      "myo",
      "hyo",
      "kyu",
      "nyu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "hyo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"mya\"?",
    "options": [
      "キャ",
      "ミャ",
      "ビャ",
      "キュ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ミャ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ミャ\"?",
    "options": [
      "kya",
      "mya",
      "ju",
      "pyo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "mya"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"myu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ミュ",
      "ピャ",
      "リャ",
      "ニョ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ミュ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ミュ\"?",
    "options": [
      "mya",
      "cha",
      "myu",
      "kya"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "myu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"myo\"?",
    "options": [
      "シュ",
      "ミョ",
      "ギャ",
      "キュ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ミョ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ミョ\"?",
    "options": [
      "hyu",
      "myo",
      "bya",
      "ju"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "myo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"rya\"?",
    "options": [
      "リャ",
      "ヒャ",
      "ジョ",
      "ニャ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "リャ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"リャ\"?",
    "options": [
      "rya",
      "hyu",
      "nyu",
      "byu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "rya"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ryu\"?",
    "options": [
      "リャ",
      "リュ",
      "ミョ",
      "ギャ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "リュ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"リュ\"?",
    "options": [
      "ryu",
      "myu",
      "gyo",
      "shu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ryu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ryo\"?",
    "options": [
      "ギャ",
      "キュ",
      "ピャ",
      "リョ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "リョ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"リョ\"?",
    "options": [
      "sha",
      "ryo",
      "gyo",
      "nya"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ryo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"gya\"?",
    "options": [
      "ヒャ",
      "キュ",
      "ギャ",
      "ジャ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ギャ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ギャ\"?",
    "options": [
      "sha",
      "sho",
      "gya",
      "chu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "gya"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"gyu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ジャ",
      "チョ",
      "ピュ",
      "ギュ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ギュ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ギュ\"?",
    "options": [
      "gyu",
      "kyu",
      "kya",
      "nya"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "gyu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"gyo\"?",
    "options": [
      "チャ",
      "ギョ",
      "ニュ",
      "ニョ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ギョ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ギョ\"?",
    "options": [
      "byo",
      "kyo",
      "gya",
      "gyo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "gyo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ja\"?",
    "options": [
      "ギャ",
      "ニュ",
      "ジャ",
      "ヒョ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ジャ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ジャ\"?",
    "options": [
      "myu",
      "cho",
      "ja",
      "hyo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ja"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ju\"?",
    "options": [
      "ヒュ",
      "ジュ",
      "ニャ",
      "ミャ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ジュ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ジュ\"?",
    "options": [
      "gya",
      "pyo",
      "ju",
      "byu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ju"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"jo\"?",
    "options": [
      "キュ",
      "ミャ",
      "ミョ",
      "ジョ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ジョ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ジョ\"?",
    "options": [
      "hya",
      "gya",
      "gyo",
      "jo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "jo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"bya\"?",
    "options": [
      "チャ",
      "ビャ",
      "ギャ",
      "ピョ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ビャ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ビャ\"?",
    "options": [
      "hyo",
      "pya",
      "rya",
      "bya"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "bya"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"byu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ビョ",
      "ピョ",
      "リョ",
      "ビュ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ビュ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ビュ\"?",
    "options": [
      "bya",
      "hyo",
      "mya",
      "byu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "byu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"byo\"?",
    "options": [
      "チャ",
      "ニュ",
      "ビョ",
      "キュ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ビョ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ビョ\"?",
    "options": [
      "hya",
      "ja",
      "cho",
      "byo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "byo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"pya\"?",
    "options": [
      "ヒュ",
      "ジュ",
      "ピャ",
      "リョ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ピャ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ピャ\"?",
    "options": [
      "pya",
      "chu",
      "hyo",
      "cha"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "pya"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"pyu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ギュ",
      "チャ",
      "キャ",
      "ピュ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ピュ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ピュ\"?",
    "options": [
      "hya",
      "kyu",
      "pyu",
      "cha"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "pyu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"pyo\"?",
    "options": [
      "ニュ",
      "ピュ",
      "チョ",
      "ピョ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ピョ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ピョ\"?",
    "options": [
      "pyo",
      "kyo",
      "hya",
      "myu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "pyo"
  }
]

export default katakanaYouon;